<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy on </title>
    <link>https://naseem-chettah.github.io/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://naseem-chettah.github.io/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Latest on AI, Privacy, and Security</title>
      <link>https://naseem-chettah.github.io/blog/post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naseem-chettah.github.io/blog/post4/</guid>
      <description>Google Open Sources Large Language Model Gemma Google recently open sourced Gemma, a large language model with similarities to the company&amp;rsquo;s Gemini family of models. Gemma comes in two sizes - 2 billion and 7 billion parameters - and is optimized to run efficiently across devices from mobile to cloud TPUs.&#xA;This is a big move by Google to spur collaboration and progress in AI research through an open model. It provides some competition to closed models like OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Developments in Cybersecurity and Privacy</title>
      <link>https://naseem-chettah.github.io/blog/post3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naseem-chettah.github.io/blog/post3/</guid>
      <description>European Court of Human Rights Rules Against Weakening Encryption The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) issued a landmark ruling that bans governments from forcing companies to weaken end-to-end encryption for mass surveillance purposes. The court held that while authorities can monitor suspects&amp;rsquo; communications without undermining wider security, general encryption backdoors present too great a privacy risk.&#xA;The decision deals a major blow to controversial EU legislation proposing &amp;ldquo;client-side scanning&amp;rdquo; backdoors that would have let police search digital devices for illegal content.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
